export default JsQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      'Q1: What is the output of the following code: console.log(typeof null);',
    options: ['null', 'object', 'undefined', 'string'],
    ans: 'object',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q2: Which of the following is a valid JavaScript variable name?',
    options: ['my-variable', 'my variable', 'myVariable', 'my.variable'],
    ans: 'myVariable',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Q3: What is the output of the following code: console.log(3 + 4 + "5");',
    options: ['12', '345', '75', 'NaN'],
    ans: '75',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Q4: What is the output of the following code: console.log(typeof NaN);',
    options: ['number', 'NaN', 'undefined', 'string'],
    ans: 'number',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q5: Which of the following is not a valid JavaScript data type?',
    options: ['null', 'undefined', 'boolean', 'integer'],
    ans: 'integer',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Q6: What is the output of the following code: console.log("5" - 3);',
    options: ['8', '15', '2', 'NaN'],
    ans: '2',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Q7: Which of the following is a higher order function in JavaScript?',
    options: [
      'Array.map()',
      'Array.forEach()',
      'Array.filter()',
      'All of the above',
    ],
    ans: 'All of the above',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Q8: What is the output of the following code: console.log(typeof [1, 2, 3]);',
    options: ['object', 'array', 'number', 'undefined'],
    ans: 'object',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Q9: Which of the following is not a comparison operator in JavaScript?',
    options: ['===', '!==', '<>', '>='],
    ans: '<>',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Q10: What is the output of the following code: console.log("5" + 3);',
    options: ['8', '15', '53', 'NaN'],
    ans: '53',
  },
];
